Washington, D.C. Postcard Collection P030 P030
Stage
- Series 1
  - Restaurants - Scholl's, undated (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Restaurants - Silver Fox, undated (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Restaurants - Surf Room Lounge, undated (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Restaurants - Syriana, undated (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Restaurants - Tai Tung, undated (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Restaurants - Tally Ho, undated (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Restaurants - Ted Lewis, undated (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Restaurants - Thompson's Cafeteria, undated (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Restaurants - Tokyo Sukiyaki, undated (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Restaurants - Torino Italian Restaurant, undated (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Restaurants - Touchdown Club, undated (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Restaurants - Water Gate Inn, undated (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Schools - Private - Academy of Sacred Heart, undated (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Schools - Private - Arlington Hall, undated (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Schools - Private - Washington Cathedral School for Girls, undated (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Schools - Public - Dunbar, undated (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Schools - Public - Eastern, undated (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Schools - Public - Roosevelt, undated (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Scottish Rite Temple, undated (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Senate Office Building - Exterior, undated (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Senate Office Building - Interior, undated (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Series - Evening Star - Murals, undated (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Series - George Washington Bicentennial, 1732-1932 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Series - Minnie E. Brooke (Photographer), undated (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Series - Roundabout Prints (Lesley Jackson, artist), undated (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Series - Washington Post, undated (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Smithsonian - Castle, undated (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Smithsonian - History and Technology, undated (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Smithsonian - National Museum (New), undated (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Smithsonian - National Museum (Old), undated (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Smithsonian - Postcard Set with Envelope, undated (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Soldier's Home, undated (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Treasury, Dept. of, undated (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - State, War and Navy, undated (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Stores - Garfinckels, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stores - Woodridge Rug and Carpet Co., Inc., undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stores - Woodward and Lothrop - Bethesda/Chevy Chase, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Stores - Woodward and Lothrop - North Building (DC), undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Stores - Woodward and Lothrop - Series #1 (DC), undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Stores - Woodward and Lothrop - Series #2 (DC), undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Stores - Woodward and Lothrop - Series #3 (DC), undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Stores - Woodward and Lothrop - Series #4 (DC), undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Stores - Woodward and Lothrop - Series #5 (DC), undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Streets - 7th NW, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Streets - 9th NW, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Streets - 13th NW, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Streets - Connecticut Avenue, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Streets - Constitution Avenue, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Streets - F NW, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Streets - Pennsylvania Avenue, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Supreme Court, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Theaters - Arena Stage, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Theaters - Belasco, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Theaters - Ford's, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Treasury - Exterior - East Elevation, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Treasury - Exterior - North Elevation, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Treasury - Exterior - South Elevation, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Treasury - Exterior - West Elevation, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Treasury - Interior, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Union Station - Exterior, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Union Station - Interior - Concourse, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Union Station - Interior - Main Waiting Room, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Union Station - Interior - President's Room, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Union Station - Misc., undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Veterans Administration Building, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Virginia - Alexandria, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Virginia - Great Falls - Potomac River, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Virginia - Great Falls - Structures, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - War Dept. Building, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - War and Navy Building, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - War Risk Insurance Building, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Zoo - Animals, undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Zoo - Structures, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Post Card Folders - Folger Shakespeare Library (1), ca. 1920s-1940s (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Post Card Folders - Franciscan Monastery (1), ca. 1920s-1940s (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Post Card Folders - Library of Congress (1), ca. 1920s-1940s (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Post Card Folders - National Historical Wax Museum – circa 1960s (1), ca. 1920s-1940s (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Post Card Folders - National Shrine of the Immaculate Conception (1), ca. 1920s-1940s (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Post Card Folders - Virginia – Arlington (4), ca. 1920s-1940s (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Post Card Folders - Washington, DC - generic tourist views (15), ca. 1920s-1940s (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Oversize Postcards, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)